University of Connecticut 1998.0187
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: University Files, 1965-1978
  - 1974-1975
    - Social workers, licensing (Box 9:, Folder 348)
    - Southeastern Branch, 4 year, URI developments (Box 9:, Folder 349)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 9:, Folder 350-352)
    - STEC (Box 9:, Folder 353)
    - Trustee material (Box 9:, Folder 354-357)
    - Veterinary Medicine, School of (Box 9:, Folder 358)
    - WTNH-TV (Box 9:, Folder 359)
  - 1976-1978
    - Academic affairs (Box 10:, Folder 360-361)
    - Academic credit for students and trustees, 1976-1977 (Box 10:, Folder 362)
    - Accreditation, 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 363)
    - ACE Intern: McFee (Box 10:, Folder 364)
    - Admissions (Box 10:, Folder 365-368)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 10:, Folder 369-373)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center (Box 10:, Folder 374)
    - Agriculture, College of (Box 10:, Folder 375-382)
    - Air conditioning, Gulley Hall (Box 10:, Folder 383)
    - Alcohol Abuse Program, 1974-1976 (Box 10:, Folder 384)
    - Allied Health (Box 10:, Folder 385-386)
    - Alumni Association, 1977-1978 (Box 10:, Folder 387-388)
    - Alumni Association (Box 11:, Folder 389-397)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 11:, Folder 398)
    - Annual reports (Box 11:, Folder 399)
    - Anthropology (Box 11:, Folder 400)
    - Archaeologist, State (Box 11:, Folder 401)
    - Area “C” meetings (Box 11:, Folder 402)
    - Asbestos ceiling - Brundage pool, 1977 (Box 11:, Folder 403)
    - Assistant to the President: David Kimball (Box 11:, Folder 404)
    - Association of Religious Counselors (Box 11:, Folder 405)
    - Associated Student Commissaries (Box 11:, Folder 406-407)
    - Athletics (Box 11:, Folder 408-419)
    - Athletics: Yankee Conference (Box 12:, Folder 420-421)
    - Athletics, Women in (Box 12:, Folder 422-427)
    - Attorney, University (Box 12:, Folder 428-429)
    - Auditor, 1976-1978 (Box 12:, Folder 430)
    - Auditorium (Box 12:, Folder 431)
    - Bachelor of General Studies (Box 12:, Folder 432)
    - Barney House (Box 12:, Folder 433)
    - Beach, Charles Foundation (Box 12:, Folder 434)
    - Bicentennial (Box 12:, Folder 435-436)
    - Bi-Lingual Cultural Center (Box 12:, Folder 437)
    - Bio-Behavioral sciences (Box 12:, Folder 438-439)
    - Biological safety (Box 12:, Folder 440)
    - Biological sciences (Box 12:, Folder 441)
    - Black studies, Center of (Box 12:, Folder 442)
    - Black Studies Task Force (Box 12:, Folder 443)
    - Bloodmobile (Box 12:, Folder 444)
    - Boards of Trustees (Box 12:, Folder 445-454)
    - Branch closing consideration (Box 13:, Folder 455)
    - Branches (Box 13:, Folder 456-467)
    - Budget (Box 13:, Folder 468-475)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 13:, Folder 476-480)
    - By-laws (Box 13:, Folder 481)
    - CADRI (Box 13:, Folder 482)
    - Calendar/appointment requests (Box 13:, Folder 483-484)
    - Campus Christian Foundation (Box 13:, Folder 483)
    - Capital campaign (Box 13:, Folder 484)
    - Centennial: University history (Box 13:, Folder 485)
    - Center for Educational Innovation (Box 13:, Folder 486)
    - Center for Slavic & Eastern European Studies (Box 13:, Folder 487)
    - Center for World Studies & Human Resource Development (Box 13:, Folder 488)
    - Certificate of Recognition: guides for awarding (Box 13:, Folder 489)
    - Chemistry Department (Box 13:, Folder 490)
    - Child care (Box 13:, Folder 491-492)
    - Classified employees (Box 13:, Folder 493)
    - Collective bargaining (Box 13:, Folder 494-495)
    - Collective Bargaining (Box 14:, Folder 496-505)
    - Commencement (Box 14:, Folder 506-510)
    - Committee, Administration Review (Box 14:, Folder 511)
    - Committee, External Progress (Box 14:, Folder 512)
    - Committee of Five (Box 14:, Folder 513)
    - Committee of Three (Box 14:, Folder 514)
    - Committee on Change and Innovations (Box 14:, Folder 515)
    - Committee on Research Strategies (Box 14:, Folder 516)
    - Committee on University Government (Box 14:, Folder 517)
    - Committee plan for multi-purpose fieldhouse (Box 14:, Folder 518)
    - Committee, Planning Coordination (Box 14:, Folder 519)
    - Committee, program review, 1976-1978 (Box 14:, Folder 520)
    - Committee - Task force on Scholarships and Awards (Box 14:, Folder 521)
    - Committee - Task force, Student Facilities (Box 14:, Folder 522)
    - Complaints (Box 14:, Folder 523-532)
    - Complaints (Box 15:, Folder 533-534)
    - Computer center (Box 15:, Folder 535)
    - Connecticut Campus Community Carnival (Box 15:, Folder 536)
    - Consulting policy (Box 15:, Folder 537)
    - Convocation - Fall, 1976 (Box 15:, Folder 538)
    - Co-op (Box 15:, Folder 539-540)
    - Co-op Program for Superior High School Students (Box 15:, Folder 541)
    - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 15:, Folder 542)
    - Crank letters (Box 15:, Folder 543)
    - Criminal Justice Programs (Box 15:, Folder 544)
    - Dance Department (Box 15:, Folder 545)
    - Data Processing (Box 15:, Folder 546)
    - Developing Administration Training Program (Box 15:, Folder 547)
    - Degrees, honorary (Box 15:, Folder 548)
    - Dental Medicine (Box 15:, Folder 549-554)
    - Detripling, 1974-1975 (Box 15:, Folder 555)
    - Development Office (Box 15:, Folder 556-557)
    - Director Search (Box 15:, Folder 558)
    - Donations (Box 15:, Folder 559)
    - Dramatic Arts (Box 15:, Folder 560)
    - Dues and subscriptions (Box 15:, Folder 561)
    - Education, Connecticut State Board of - Self Study Report (Box 15:, Folder 562)
    - Education, School of (Box 15:, Folder 564-564)
    - Education, School of (Box 16:, Folder 565)
    - Elderly, Housing Possibility, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 566)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 16:, Folder 567-571)
    - English Department (Box 16:, Folder 572)
    - Enrollments (Box 16:, Folder 573-574)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Office (Box 16:, Folder 575-580)
    - Equipment Requests and Consideration (Box 16:, Folder 581)
    - ERD (Box 16:, Folder 582)
    - Exchange Programs (Box 16:, Folder 583-587)
    - Executive Assistant, J. Otto (Box 16:, Folder 588)
    - Experimental College: atomic bomb issue, 1977 (Box 16:, Folder 589)
    - Expertise available at UConn (Box 16:, Folder 590)
    - Extended and continuing education (Box 16:, Folder 591)
    - Faculty-Alumni Center (Box 16:, Folder 592)
    - Faculty Dependent Tuition (Box 16:, Folder 593-594)
    - Faculty resources issue, 1976-1978 (Box 16:, Folder 592)
    - Faculty termination (Box 16:, Folder 593)
    - Faculty time survey (Box 16:, Folder 594)
    - Finance and Administration (Box 16:, Folder 595-599)
    - Finance and Administration (Box 17:, Folder 600-606)
    - Fine Arts groundbreaking, 1978 April (Box 17:, Folder 607)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 17:, Folder 608)
    - Fulbright-Hays Conference, 1977 June (Box 17:, Folder 609)
    - Garden plots (Box 17:, Folder 610)
    - Geology Department (Box 17:, Folder 611)
    - Germanic and Slavic Languages Department (Box 17:, Folder 612)
    - Gerontology (Box 17:, Folder 613)
    - Ginsburg-Laughlin: Racist charges, 1974 (Box 17:, Folder 614)
    - Governmental inquiries (Box 17:, Folder 615)
    - Graduate School (Box 17:, Folder 616-619)
    - Graduate student concerns (Box 17:, Folder 620)
    - Grant information (Box 17:, Folder 621)
    - Health Center (Box 17:, Folder 622-629)
    - Health Center (Box 18:, Folder 630-644)
    - Health Profession, Progress Review, Committee for (Box 18:, Folder 645)
    - Health services (Box 18:, Folder 646-647)
    - Honors program, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 648)
    - Housing problems (Box 18:, Folder 649)
    - Housing and Food Services Division, 1975 (Box 18:, Folder 650)
    - Institute of Materials Science (Box 18:, Folder 651)
    - Institute of Natural Resources (Box 18:, Folder 652)
    - Institute of Public Service (Box 18:, Folder 653)
    - Institutional Research, Office of (Box 19:, Folder 654-660)
    - International Baccalaureate (Box 19:, Folder 661)
    - International Center (Box 19:, Folder 662)
    - International progress (Box 19:, Folder 663)
    - Krimmerman - McCarthy (Box 19:, Folder 664)
    - Law, School of (Box 19:, Folder 665-672)
    - Layoffs, 1975-1976 (Box 19:, Folder 673)
    - Legal fees, payment of (Box 19:, Folder 674)
    - Letters sent - V.P. Finance and Administration (Box 19:, Folder 675)
    - Liberal Arts and Sciences (Box 20:, Folder 676)
    - Library (Box 20:, Folder 677-682)
    - Linguistics Department (Box 20:, Folder 683)
    - Mansfield, Town of (Box 20:, Folder 684-685)
    - Marine Sciences Department (Box 20:, Folder 686)
    - Math Department (Box 20:, Folder 687)
    - Medicine, School of (Box 20:, Folder 688-693)
    - McMahon Lecture, 1976-1978 (Box 20:, Folder 694)
    - Merit increase, 1975 (Box 20:, Folder 695)
    - Metanoia Day (Box 20:, Folder 696)
    - Metrication (Box 20:, Folder 697)
    - Middle East group (Box 20:, Folder 698)
    - Minority Affairs - Barney House Conference (Box 20:, Folder 699)
    - Minority Affairs Office (Box 20:, Folder 700)
    - Minority Student Progress Plan (Box 20:, Folder 701)
    - Money saved, 1975 (Box 20:, Folder 702)
    - MPA - Public Affairs School (Box 20:, Folder 703)
    - Museum of Art, Benton (Box 20:, Folder 704)
    - National Health Planning Act (Box 20:, Folder 705)
    - “Neo-Naziism” (Box 20:, Folder 706)
    - NERAC (Box 20:, Folder 707)
    - New England Board of Higher Education, information (Box 20:, Folder 708)
    - New Vocations Center (Box 20:, Folder 709)
    - Non-Teaching Professional Personnel Policy (Box 20:, Folder 710)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 20:, Folder 711)
    - Objectives, short-term (Box 20:, Folder 712)
    - Ombudsman, 1967-1978 (Box 20:, Folder 713)
    - Ornithologist, State (Box 20:, Folder 714)
    - Parking (Box 21:, Folder 715)
    - Part-time faculty (Box 21:, Folder 716)
    - Payroll (Box 21:, Folder 717)
    - Peace Center (Box 21:, Folder 718)
    - Personnel: classified employee Grievances (Box 21:, Folder 719)
    - Personnel Policies: reclassify, update, fund (Box 21:, Folder 720)
    - Personnel Services Division (Box 21:, Folder 721-722)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 21:, Folder 723)
    - Photos (Box 21:, Folder 724)
    - Physical plant (Box 21:, Folder 725)
    - Physics Department (Box 21:, Folder 726)
    - Placement (Box 21:, Folder 727)
    - Plan, 1977 June (Box 21:, Folder 728-730)
    - Plan, Brand: Reactions (Box 21:, Folder 731)
    - Planning, academic (Box 21:, Folder 732-734)
    - Policy statements (Box 21:, Folder 735)
    - Political Science (Box 21:, Folder 736)
    - Post office Controversy (Box 21:, Folder 737)
    - Preservation of historic sites (Box 21:, Folder 738)
    - President's office staff (Box 21:, Folder 739)
    - Press releases, G.W. Ferguson (Box 21:, Folder 740-741)
    - Profile, University, 1976-1978 (Box 21:, Folder 742)
    - Promotion, tenure and reappointment (Box 21:, Folder 743)
    - Proposals (Box 21:, Folder 744)
    - Provost Search Committee (Box 21:, Folder 745)
    - Psychology Department (Box 21:, Folder 746)
    - Public safety (Box 21:, Folder 747-748)
    - Publications, University (Box 21:, Folder 749)
    - Public Information Office (Box 21:, Folder 750-752)
    - Puerto Rican concerns (Box 21:, Folder 753-754)
    - Puerto Rican concerns: Directorship (Box 22:, Folder 755)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 22:, Folder 756)
    - Racism (Box 22:, Folder 757)
    - Radio and Television Center (Box 22:, Folder 758)
    - Reappointments (Box 22:, Folder 759)
    - Registrar (Box 22:, Folder 760)
    - Renovations (Box 22:, Folder 761)
    - Reorganization, reassignments (Box 22:, Folder 762)
    - Research: conflicts of interests (Box 22:, Folder 763)
    - Research Foundation (Box 22:, Folder 764)
    - Retirees (Box 22:, Folder 765)
    - Romance and Classical Languages Department (Box 22:, Folder 766)
    - Roper Center (Box 22:, Folder 767-769)
    - ROTC (Box 22:, Folder 770-771)
    - Sabbatic leave (Box 22:, Folder 772)
    - Salaries (Box 22:, Folder 773-775)
    - Salaries (Box 22:, Folder 776-777)
    - Scholarships (Box 22:, Folder 778-786)
    - Scholastic Aptitude Test score decline (Box 22:, Folder 787)
    - Scoville, William, B., Professorship in Neurological Surgery (Box 22:, Folder 788)
    - Search, presidential - ADS (Box 22:, Folder 789)
    - Search procedures (Box 22:, Folder 790)
    - Senior staff (Box 22:, Folder 791-792)
    - Shuttlebus service (Box 22:, Folder 793)
    - Smith, E.O., High School (Box 22:, Folder 794)
    - Smith, H. Fairfield (Box 22:, Folder 795)
    - Snowstorm, 1978 (Box 22:, Folder 796)
    - Social Science Data Center (Box 22:, Folder 797)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 23:, Folder 798-800)
    - Sociology Department (Box 23:, Folder 801)
    - Speeches (Box 23:, Folder 802-803)
    - Storrs Congregational church organ (Box 23:, Folder 804)
    - Student affairs and services (Box 23:, Folder 805-812)
    - Student affairs and services, 1976-1978 (Box 23:, Folder 813-819)
    - Student labor (Box 23:, Folder 820)
    - Student organizations (Box 24:, Folder 821-844)
    - Subscriptions - not renewed (Box 24:, Folder 845)
    - Summer session (Box 24:, Folder 846)
    - TAFS Committee (Box 24:, Folder 847)
    - Telephone call sheets (Box 24:, Folder 848-849)
    - Telephone service (Box 24:, Folder 850)
    - Tenure, academic (Box 24:, Folder 851)
    - Three R's (Box 24:, Folder 852)
    - Torrey, G. Safford (Box 24:, Folder 853)
    - Transportation Department (Box 24:, Folder 854)
    - Travel information (Box 24:, Folder 855)
    - Travel - non-ERA approved states (Box 24:, Folder 856)
    - Tuition (Box 24:, Folder 857-859)
    - Tuition and fees (Box 25:, Folder 860-862)
    - UConn foundation (Box 25:, Folder 863-865)
    - U.N. Day (Box 25:, Folder 866)
    - University Chronicle (Box 25:, Folder 867)
    - University seal (Box 25:, Folder 868)
    - Urban Semester Program (Box 25:, Folder 869)
    - Veterinary medicine (Box 25:, Folder 870-876)
    - Vietnamese inquires (Box 25:, Folder 877)
    - WATS line (Box 25:, Folder 878)
    - Women, continuing education (Box 25:, Folder 879)
    - Women's council (Box 25:, Folder 880)
    - Women, Organization of Faculty and Professional (Box 25:, Folder 881)
    - Women's Center (Box 25:, Folder 882-884)
    - Women's Studies Program (Box 25:, Folder 885)
    - Yggdrasil (Box 25:, Folder 886)
- Series II: State Files, 1974-1978
  - Audits of Public Accounts (Box 26:, Folder 887-889)
  - Aging, Department of (Box 26:, Folder 890)
  - Appropriations Committee (Box 26:, Folder 891)
  - Attorney General (Box 26:, Folder 892)
  - Banking Department, State of Connecticut (Box 26:, Folder 893)
  - Bicentennial Commission (Box 26:, Folder 894)
  - Board of Higher Education (Box 26:, Folder 895-907)
  - Board for State Academic Awards (Box 26:, Folder 908)
  - Board of Trustees - State Colleges, State Technical and Regional (Box 26:, Folder 909)
  - Collective bargaining (Box 26:, Folder 910-911)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts (Box 26:, Folder 912)
  - Commission for Connecticut Future (Box 26:, Folder 913)
  - Commission for Higher Education (Box 26:, Folder 914)
  - Commission for Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 26:, Folder 915)
  - Commission for Higher Education (Box 27:, Folder 916-924)
  - Commission on Efficiency and Productivity (Box 27:, Folder 925)
  - Commission on Special Revenues (Box 27:, Folder 926)
  - Commission to Study Structures of State Governments (Box 27:, Folder 927)
  - Comptroller (Box 27:, Folder 928)
  - Commission for Higher Education (Box 27:, Folder 929-930)
  - Connecticut Association for Continuing Education (Box 27:, Folder 931)
  - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 27:, Folder 932-933)
  - Connecticut, State of (Box 27:, Folder 934)
  - Coordinating Council (Box 27:, Folder 935)
  - Coordinating Council minutes (Box 27:, Folder 936)
  - Democratic State Platform (Box 27:, Folder 937)
  - Eastern Connecticut State College (Box 27:, Folder 938)
  - Education Committee (Box 27:, Folder 939)
  - Education Subcommittee of the Appropriations Committee (Box 27:, Folder 940)
  - Emergency Operations, State (Box 27:, Folder 941)
  - Employee Suggestion Awards Program (Box 27:, Folder 942)
  - Energy Agency, Connecticut (Box 27:, Folder 943)
  - Etherington Committee Report (Box 27:, Folder 944)
  - Executives Day (Box 27:, Folder 945)
  - Finance and Control Department (Box 27:, Folder 946)
  - Freedom of Information Act (Box 27:, Folder 947)
  - Freedom of Information Act (Box 27:, Folder 948)
  - General Assembly, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 949)
  - General Assembly (Box 28:, Folder 950-951)
  - Regents, Board of HB-5229 (Box 28:, Folder 952)
- Series III: Paul Capra Files, 1972-1978
  - AAMC Planners' meeting (Box 29:, Folder 953)
  - Academic Affairs: Kenneth Wilson, Vice President (Box 29:, Folder 954)
  - Activities Office (Box 29:, Folder 955)
  - Administrative procedure (Box 29:, Folder 956)
  - Admissions and other inquiries (Box 29:, Folder 957-958)
  - Admissions
    - Graduate (Box 29:, Folder 959)
    - Law School (Box 29:, Folder 960)
    - Legislative Requests (Box 29:, Folder 961)
    - Medical School (Box 29:, Folder 962)
    - School of Social Work (Box 29:, Folder 963)
    - Undergraduate (Box 29:, Folder 964-966)
  - Aerial photo (Box 29:, Folder 967)
  - Agriculture, College of: Cooperative Extension Service (Box 29:, Folder 968)
  - Agriculture, College of: E.J. Kersting, Dean (Box 29:, Folder 969)
  - Agriculture and Natural Resources, School of (Box 29:, Folder 970)
  - Alumni Association: Thalacker, Roger K. (Box 29:, Folder 971-972)
  - Alumni Legislators Booklet (Box 29:, Folder 973)
  - Alumni Legislators Day (Box 29:, Folder 974)
  - Alumni trustees Dinner for Legislatives Leaders (Box 29:, Folder 975)
  - American Indians (Box 29:, Folder 976)
  - American Indians Education Program (Box 29:, Folder 977)
  - American University field service (Box 29:, Folder 978)
  - Annual Report (Box 29:, Folder 979-980)
  - Annual Report, government forms (Box 29:, Folder 981)
  - Annual Report to Governor, President's (Box 29:, Folder 982-983)
  - Annual Report preparation (Box 29:, Folder 984)
  - Annual Report, President's (Box 29:, Folder 985)
  - Annual Report, President's report distribution (Box 29:, Folder 986)
  - Appropriations Committee (Box 30:, Folder 987-992)
  - Appropriations Subcommittee (Box 30:, Folder 993)
  - Art Department: David Kelly (Box 30:, Folder 994)
  - Associated Student Government: Steve Krpata, Chair (Box 30:, Folder 995)
  - Athletics, Division of: John Toner, Director (Box 30:, Folder 996)
  - Athletics: Yankee Conference (Box 30:, Folder 997)
  - Auden, W.H.; visit to Storrs (Box 30:, Folder 998)
  - B.A.: General Studies (Box 30:, Folder 999)
  - Bills
    - Active (Box 30:, Folder 1000)
    - Boxed (Box 30:, Folder 1001)
    - CHE (Box 30:, Folder 1002)
    - Final disposition of (Box 30:, Folder 1003)
    - General (Box 30:, Folder 1004)
    - Possible (Box 30:, Folder 1005)
    - Proposed (Box 30:, Folder 1006)
    - Status display, terminal guide, CT General Assembly (Box 30:, Folder 1007)
    - To watch (Box 30:, Folder 1008)
  - Biobehavioral Sciences, Dept. of (Box 30:, Folder 1009)
  - Biological Sciences Group (Box 30:, Folder 1010)
  - Biological Sciences Seminar Program (Box 30:, Folder 1011)
  - Biopsychology Colloquium Series (Box 30:, Folder 1012)
  - Biosis (Box 30:, Folder 1013)
  - Black Voices of Freedom Gospel Choir tour (Box 30:, Folder 1014)
  - Board of Governors (Box 30:, Folder 1015)
  - Board of Trustees
    - Meetings (Box 30:, Folder 1016)
    - Reports to (Box 30:, Folder 1017)
    - Structure of (Box 30:, Folder 1018)
  - Branches (Box 30:, Folder 1019)
  - Budget (Box 30:, Folder 1020-1021)
  - Bureau of Institutional Research (Box 30:, Folder 1022)
  - Business Administration, School of (Box 30:, Folder 1023)
  - Buy-in (Box 30:, Folder 1024)
  - Campus tour groups (Box 30:, Folder 1025)
  - Capital Building Programs (Box 30:, Folder 1026)
  - Capital budget (Box 30:, Folder 1027)
  - Capital campaign information (Box 30:, Folder 1028)
  - Capital projects (Box 30:, Folder 1029)
  - Capital transfers (Box 30:, Folder 1030)
  - Career planning of placement (Box 30:, Folder 1031)
  - Carpenter, Dr. (Box 30:, Folder 1032)
  - Center for Black Studies (Box 30:, Folder 1033)
  - Chambers, M.M. (Box 30:, Folder 1034)
  - Chase, David T.: prospect file (Box 30:, Folder 1035)
  - Chemical Engineering Department (Box 31:, Folder 1036)
  - Child care: experimental program (Box 31:, Folder 1037)
  - Children's Literature (Box 31:, Folder 1038)
  - Civil Engineering (Box 31:, Folder 1039)
  - Clippings (Box 31:, Folder 1040)
  - Clippings: budget (Box 31:, Folder 1041)
  - Collective bargaining (Box 31:, Folder 1042)
  - College of Veterinary Medicine: Stuart Smith (Box 31:, Folder 1043)
  - Commission for Higher Education (CHE)
    - Bills (Box 31:, Folder 1044)
    - Buying in (Box 31:, Folder 1045)
  - Commissioners (Box 31:, Folder 1046)
  - Committee on Environment (Box 31:, Folder 1047)
  - Committee heads: senate (Box 31:, Folder 1048)
  - Committee to Establish a College of Veterinary Medicine (Box 31:, Folder 1049)
  - ommunity education information (Box 31:, Folder 1050)
  - Commuters' Union (Box 31:, Folder 1051)
  - Congregational Church Organization (Box 31:, Folder 1062)
  - Connecticut Citizen's Conference on the General Assembly (Box 31:, Folder 1063)
  - Connecticut districts (Box 31:, Folder 1064)
  - Connecticut legislators
    - Ajello, Carl Rep. (Box 31:, Folder 1065)
    - Antonetti, Richard (Box 31:, Folder 1066)
    - Apthorp, Grant Rep. (Box 31:, Folder 1067)
    - Beck, Audrey, Rep. (Box 31:, Folder 1068)
    - Berry, Louise, Sen. (Box 31:, Folder 1069)
    - Brown, Hoyte, Jr. Rep. (Box 31:, Folder 1070)
    - Canali, James M. (Box 31:, Folder 1071)
    - Carruthers, Thomas, Sen. (Box 31:, Folder 1072)
    - Coatsworth, Joseph S. (Box 31:, Folder 1073)
    - Cohen, Morris (Health Center) (Box 31:, Folder 1074)
    - Collins, Francis Rep.: Speaker of the House (Box 31:, Folder 1075)
    - Cretella, Albert W., Jr. Rep. (Box 31:, Folder 1076)
    - Cutillo, Louis, Sen. (Box 31:, Folder 1077)
    - Defrancesco, Mark S. (Box 31:, Folder 1078)
    - Denardis, Lawrence J. (Box 31:, Folder 1079)
    - Dice, Richard (Box 31:, Folder 1080)
    - Dzialo, Raymond (Box 31:, Folder 1081)
    - Finney, Florence, Sen.: President Pro-Tem (Box 31:, Folder 1082)
    - Griswold, Mary B. (Box 31:, Folder 1083)
    - Hammer, Lucy T. (Box 31:, Folder 1084)
    - Hanzalek, Astrid T. (Box 31:, Folder 1085)
    - Hellier, Samuel B., Sen. (Box 31:, Folder 1086)
    - Holdsworth, Earl T. (Box 31:, Folder 1087)
    - Houley, Robert, Sen. (Box 31:, Folder 1088)
    - Klebanoff, Howard M. Rep. (Box 31:, Folder 1089)
    - Lieberman, H.C., Sen. (Box 31:, Folder 1090)
    - Locke, Peter F., Jr. (Box 31:, Folder 1091)
    - Mannix, John F. (Box 31:, Folder 1092)
    - Mazzola, Alan J. (Box 31:, Folder 1093)
    - McCormick-Nielson: meeting of legislative leaders (Box 31:, Folder 1094)
    - Movano, Michael (Box 31:, Folder 1095)
    - Rapport, Natalie (Box 31:, Folder 1096)
    - Ratchford, William R. (Box 31:, Folder 1097)
    - Rome, Lewis B., Sen. (Box 31:, Folder 1098)
    - Sayre, Clyde O. (Box 31:, Folder 1099)
    - Smith, Winthrop S. (Box 31:, Folder 1100)
    - Stevens, Gerald F.: minority leader's office (Box 31:, Folder 1101)
    - Stolberg, Irving (Box 31:, Folder 1102)
    - Strada, Williams, Sen. (Box 31:, Folder 1103)
    - Triex, Ruth O. (Box 31:, Folder 1104)
    - Vella, Rosario T.: cable television (Box 31:, Folder 1105)